const questionsAnswers = [
    { question: "Does A have to be nxn invertible matrix?", answer: "Yes" },
    { question: "What matrix does matrix A have to be row equivalent to?", answer: "The identity matrix" },
    { question: "How many pivot positions does a matrix nxn need?", answer: "n pivot positions" },
    { question: "Does Ax=b need one solution for every b in R^n or infinite solutions", answer: "One solution for every b in R^n" },
    { question: "What do the columns of A have to be?", answer: "Linearly Indepentent" },
    { question: "Columns of A do not Span R^n. T/F", answer: "False" },
    { question: "Ax=0 has only what type of solution?", answer: "The trivial solution x=0" },
    { question: "x --> Ax has to be one-to-one. T/F", answer: "True" },
    { question: "x --> Ax can't be onto. T/F", answer: "False" },
    { question: "There exists a nxn matrix C such that CA = ?", answer: "The invertible matrix" },
    { question: "There exists a nxn matrix D such that DA = ?", answer: "The invertible matrix" },
    { question: "A^T is invertible. T/F", answer: "True" }
  ];
  
  export default questionsAnswers;